anointedtube.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy/Copyright Notification

This privacy policy sets out how Anointedtube uses and protects any information that you give while using [http://anointedtube.com/](https://anointedtube.com/) 

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Anointedtube may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 22/5/2018. By using our platforms and services on or after that date, you’ll be agreeing to these updates.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

            * contact information including email address

demographic information such as preferences and interests

**What we do with the information we gather**  

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

We may use the information to improve our services.

We may periodically send emails about Anointedtube and other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

Cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to visitor needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

**Advertising**

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. These Advertisers may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you information about Anointedtube which we think you may interesting.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://anointedtube.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#debfb0b1b7b0aabbbaaaabbcbb9eb6b1aab3bfb7b2f0bdb1b3)

COPYRIGHT NOTIFICATION

Anointedtube does not permit copyright infringing activities and infringement of intellectual property rights on its Website and will remove all Content if properly notified that such content infringes on another's intellectual property rights. Anointedtube reserves the right also to remove any video/s or terminate any channel, if they are determined to be a repeat infringer. 

If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide Anointedtube`s copyright agent with the written information specified below: 

A physical or electronic signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest that is allegedly infringed; 

A description of all of the copyrighted works that you claim has been infringed upon; 

A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Anointedtube website, including, a URL of the specific location of the infringing material;

Information sufficient to allow us to contact you including, at a minimum, your address, telephone number, and e-mail address;

A statement by you that you have a good-faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and

A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf. Please send your copyright notification to [[email protected]](https://anointedtube.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#573639383e3923323323223532173f38233a363e3b7934383a)
